There's no such thing as final vengeance!
Afro Samurai: Resurrection is a animation, action,
adventure film directed by Fuminori Kizaki.
Afro Samurai avenged his father and found a life of peace.
But the legendary master is forced back into the game by a
beautiful and deadly woman from his past.
The sparks of violence dropped along Afro’s bloody path now burn out of control – and
nowhere are the flames of hatred more intense than in the eyes of Sio.
Afro / Ninja-Ninja (voice), played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Tomoe / Ogin (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Bin / Oden Shop Master (voice), played by Mark Hamill.
Professor Dharman / Kidnapper (voice), played by S. Scott Bullock.
Afro's Father (voice), played by Greg Eagles.
Sio (voice), played by Lucy Liu.
Afro Samurai: Resurrection (アフロサムライ レザレクション, Afuro Samurai Rezarekushon), (stylized as ΛFΓO SΛMUΓΛI RESUΓΓECTIOΠ) is a 2009
English-language Japanese animated television film sequel to the anime series Afro Samurai, starring Samuel L.
Jackson and Lucy Liu.
It aired on Spike TV on January 25, 2009.
The film explores themes of japan, samurai, based on
manga, adult animation, feudal japan.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.